linkstoxx.com 2010-12-22

# Linkstoxx: The Network Stock Exchange

**Terms of Use**  
---  
  
**Conditions of Use govern below and describe the rights and duties of the site user Linkstoxx (www.linkstoxx.com), the relationships they have with Linkstoxx and third parties that interact with Linkstoxx. Using Linkstoxx indicates full acceptance of these conditions. These terms of use take effect from 1 January 2009 and apply to persons who have created an account Linkstoxx, hereinafter designated by "users" or "you".**  

**Sharing your content and your information**  
  
The content or information you publish on Linkstoxx belong to you, and you can control how we share your content through the privacy settings available on the page "parameter of the account" user menu. Also: For content protected by intellectual property rights, such as photos or videos (IP), you give us specific permission following in accordance with your privacy settings and application settings, you are granting us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use intellectual property content that you post on or in connection with Linkstoxx Linkstoxx ("IP license"). This IP license terminates when you remove your content or intellectual property your account unless your account is shared with other people who have not deleted. When you remove your intellectual property content, content is removed in a manner similar to dump trash on a computer. However, you understand that the content removed, may persist in backup copies for a while (but they are not available). When you post content or information with the setting "everyone" means everyone, including people who do not Linkstoxx may have access to content or information published and you can do not able to control what they do. We appreciate your comments and suggestions regarding Linkstoxx, but you understand that we can use it without any obligation to pay (as you have no obligation to send them to me).  

**Use of personal data & Online Advertising**  
  
Users grant the right to Linkstoxx use in an automated and anonymous certain personal data of their account, for purposes of targeting advertising only. These data may be their occupation, country of residence, age, sex and discussion groups (GroupStoxx) they are enrolled where they created. _In any case, Linkstoxx use of personal data about users to any purpose whatsoever without explicit consent._  

**Point allocation rules**  
  
The principle is Linkstoxx compensate its members based on their contribution to the network and their ability to contact other members. Some actions of a user on the site have resulted in credit his account of points. Each of these actions, listed below, correspond to a credit of a number of points. These actions include, without being exhaustive:   
\- Number of inbound contacts   
\- Number of outbound contacts   
\- Number of new contacts on the period "StoxxRelease" being   
\- Loyalty bonus (limited to one visit per user per day)   
\- Subscription to discussion groups (GroupStoxx)   
\- Facilitating discussion groups (GroupStoxx) by subscription users   
\- Credit cards with points Linkstoxx (LinkCards) 

The rules for endowment of points are at the discretion of Linkstoxx and may change during the StoxxRelease.  

**Valuing points users - StoxxRelease**  
  
At the beginning of the period called "StoxxRelease, whose frequency is determined by Linkstoxx, a sum of money is put into play for all users. After the StoxxRelease, the calculation of points of the set of users is done for each account and financial value to determine the amount Linkstoxx reverse each user. Specifically, the points acquired by a user are valued in proportion to the total points earned by all users (example: Bobby BRIAN has accumulated 2,000 points, or 3% of points earned by all members). This is the part that determines the amount to be paid to the user. Linkstoxx alone can determine the points earned by the users and the amounts paid to them. However, users can submit their questions in writing to récalamtions [payment@linkstoxx.com](mailto:payment@linkstoxx.com).  

**Payments / Payout users**  
  
End of period (StoxxRelease), the sum involved is shared between users Linkstoxx, according to the rules defined above. The amounts paid to the users have the following characteristics:   
\- Payments are made in euros, to the penny   
\- Payments are made only on the PayPal platform. In this respect, it is mandatory that a user enters his username PayPal to receive payments in   
\- The Committee of PayPal services is the responsibility of user Linkstoxx.   
\- The payment period from the end of the StoxxRelease is the order of 2 to 5 days. However, if large volumes of payments to be processed, Linkstoxx can not make a firm commitment to respect the deadline.   
\- Claims of a user on a payment should be sent only by e-mail to [payment@linkstoxx.com ](mailto:payment@linkstoxx.com). 

At any time, the user can track the status of its payments (ongoing, completed, canceled) in the pages MANAGEMENT OF PAYMENTS "and" ACCOUNT SETTINGS ".  

**Terms of use messaging (LinkBoxx)**  
  
The functionality of online messaging, hereinafter referred to as "LinkBoxx" allows you to send and receive messages to other users Linkstoxx. The LinkBoxx is only accessible from the site www.linkstoxx.com. Private messages contained therein are confidential and belong to their issuers. However, according to French laws and international laws, Linkstoxx may be required to make these messages available to the competent authorities in the investigation concerning the issuer and / or its recipient.  

**Conditions relating to job offers (Jobs)**  
  
Job offers, hereinafter designated "Jobs" is freely distributed by other companies. Apply for these jobs is a free service for users Linkstoxx. Users of this service must respect certain rules of conduct to ensure quality and continuity of this service:   
\- Do not apply for jobs that do not correpondant professional profile of users or their career aspirations   
\- Provide valid information (phone, e-mail and online resume) allowing broadcasters to these jobs if they wish to contact you   
\- Do not apply more than once to the same Job in any manner whatsoever   
\- Do not distribute these jobs to other websites, blogs or other media whatsoever without the prior consent of Linkstoxx and the company issuing the Job. 

Individuals or companies using this service to disseminate Jobs are also held to certain rules of use:   
\- Only one account per company, as far as possible   
\- Do not post twice the same Job, except for translation into a different language   
\- Post Jobs for which positions are actually open within your company   
\- Do not attempt to contact the users who did not apply for their jobs 

Failure to follow these rules would compel us to suspend or delete your user account, and that applications filed or disseminated Jobs. 

Some jobs are from partner sites. In this case, the button "APPLY" redirects the user on the partner's application form. Linkstoxx emerges therefore not responsible for the processing of that form or information contained on the destination page.  

**Terms of Use discussion groups (GroupStoxx)**  
  
Focus groups, hereinafter referred to as "GroupStoxx" Linkstoxx allow users to communicate with each other on a specific theme. A GroupStoxx can be created and managed by a user, hereinafter referred to as "Manager". 

Operating rules of GroupStoxx: Signing a user to a GroupStoxx may be free or in exchange for a number of points, within the parameters of GroupStoxx informed by the Manager. Where appropriate, points will be debited from user account and credited to the account manager at the time of validation of the subscription by the Manager. Once validated by the subscription manager, users can not claim a retro-assignment of points used for the same subscription. A user can not subscribe several times to the same GroupStoxx. In contrast, a user can create and manage multiple GroupStoxx. When StoxxRelease current accumulated points each GroupStoxx collective, which are based on a number of criteria may change over time, at the discretion of Linkstoxx (user loyalty, total sales, total new subscriptions during the current StoxxRelease, etc..). After the StoxxRelease, these points are shared between users who subscribed to and accumulate points in their account. 

Regarding public discussions, users and managers GroupStoxx must ensure the integrity and respect for broadcast content. The Managers are encouraged to use the features of their moderation and GroupStoxx users to report content disagree with these terms of use, by writing to [abuse@linkstoxx.com ](mailto:abuse@linkstoxx.com). Any content deemed at odds with the terms of use Linkstoxx or infringing the French and international laws in force shall be removed from the site. The user account authors of these messages may be suspended or deleted without notice, without possibility of récalamation gains during these users.  

**Amendments**  
Linkstoxx reserves the right to modify all or part of these Terms of Use.  
   
**Termination**  
  
If you violate any or all of these terms of use or otherwise create a risk of litigation against us, we reserve the right to suspend your account without notice Linkstoxx. In case of an attempted intrusion into computer systems and databases Linkstoxx for fraudulent or breach of these terms of use, payments due will not you be paid, and payments already made for you will you be claimed in part or in full, in partial compensation for the damage suffered. For any termination of account, we will notify you by e-mail to the address associated with your account Linkstoxx.  

**Litigation**  
You will wear any complaint relating to these conditions or Linkstoxx exclusively before the French courts. The French law is the law applied to these terms of use, and any action between you and us, without regard to principles of conflict of laws. You agree to respect the jurisdiction of French courts in such actions. In case of complaint against us due to your actions, your content or your information on Linkstoxx you Linkstoxx indemnify for any loss, liability, claim, demand, costs and expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, related to the complaint.  
   
**Tax system**  

The principle is to pay Linkstoxx income users, in terms of its contribution to the growth of Linkstoxx number of users and their loyalty to the site's content (participation and facilitation of focus groups). Therefore, Linkstoxx encourages users to read with the relevant authorities of their country of residence provisions relating to taxation of such income. Linkstoxx committed to providing its users with clear information on the amounts paid, on request by writing to [payment@linkstoxx.com ](mailto:payment@linkstoxx.com). Linkstoxx assumes no responsibility for any false statement or fraud attempt from a user with the tax authorities concerned.  

**Other**  
  
These Terms of Use constitutes the entire agreement between the parties on Linkstoxx and supersedes any previous agreement. If any of these conditions is invalid or unenforceable, the remainder shall remain in force and applicable. Any failure Linkstoxx enforcing these conditions can be considered a waiver. Any amendment or waiver of these conditions must be in writing and signed by Linkstoxx. Users will not transfer any rights or their obligations under these conditions to any third party without the agreement of Linkstoxx. All rights and obligations under these conditions are transferable by Linkstoxx through a merger, acquisition, sale of assets, a request of courts or in other cases. Nothing in this Agreement shall prevent Linkstoxx respect the law. These Conditions shall confer any rights to third party beneficiaries.  

**Security**  
  
We will do our best to make sure Linkstoxx service, but can not guarantee absolute safety. To do this, we need your help, which includes the following obligations: 

\- You will not send and will not publish commercial communications without authorization (such as junk mail) on Linkstoxx.   
\- You will not get information about individual users or content that they publish, and does not access Linkstoxx using automated methods (such as robots, spiders, etc..) Without our permission.   
\- You will not be clicking, or encourage anyone to click, so artificial advertising on Linkstoxx.com   
\- You will not upload viruses or other malicious code.   
\- You do not ask login information and does not access an account belonging to someone else.   
\- You will not intimidate, and do not harass other users.   
\- You will not post content hateful, pornographic, or that contain nudity or gratuitous violence.   
\- You will not use Linkstoxx purposes of illegal activity, illegal, malicious or discriminatory.   
\- You will not act in a manner that could disable or otherwise interfere with the proper functioning of the Service Linkstoxx (as an attack denial of service).   
\- You will not allow and will not encourage violations of this Declaration.  

**Registration and Account Security**  

Linkstoxx users give their real name and real information about them, and we ask you to help us ensure that this does not change. Here are some terms you agree to abide to the registration and security of your account: 

\- You will not give false personal information on Linkstoxx and will not create an account for another person without their permission.   
\- You will not use Linkstoxx if you are under 13 years.   
\- You will not use Linkstoxx if you need to register with local authorities because of a conviction for sexual assault.   
\- You put your contact information, accurate, current.   
\- You do not communicate your password, you will not allow anyone else to use your account and make sure you do not risk compromising the security of your account.   
\- You will not transfer your account without first obtaining written permission from us. 

If you select a username for your account, we reserve the right to withdraw it if we deem inappropriate (eg where the proprietor of a trademark filed a complaint concerning a username that does not match the real name of the user). 

To ensure users Linkstoxx a high quality level and to prevent any attempt at fraud, the use of disposable email addresses is prohibited (eg YopMail @, @ ... link2mail.net non-exhaustive list) . Accounts that use this type of e-mail will be terminated without prior notice, payments under these accounts will be canceled.  

**Protecting the rights of others**  
  
We respect the rights of others and we ask you to do the same.

\- You will not post content and you will take on anything that might Linkstoxx violate the rights of others or otherwise violate the law.   
\- We can withdraw the content or information you publish on Linkstoxx if we believe it is in violation of these terms of use.   
\- If we remove your content because of an infringement of copyright in third and you think it is a mistake.   
\- If you infringe the intellectual property rights of others on several occasions, we will delete your account.   
\- You will not use our trademarks (such as Linkstoxx, The stock exchange network, We share more Than success, WSMTS) or any other mark confusingly similar, without our written permission.   
\- If you get information from users: you will agree and you present them clearly that you (not Linkstoxx) to collect this information, and you publish your policy of respecting the privacy indicating information gathered and the use that is made.   
\- You will not publish official documents or financial information for others on Linkstoxx.  

**Payments**  
If you make a payment on or use of credits Linkstoxx Linkstoxx, you agree to our terms of payment.  

**Privacy Policy**  
  
**Linkstoxx Privacy policy aims to help you understand how we collect and use personal information you choose to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Linkstoxx on the site and its sub-Linkstoxx.com areas directly related (hereinafter referred to indiscriminately as "Linkstoxx" or "Website"). By using or accessing Linkstoxx, you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This privacy policy is effective from 1 January 2009.**  

**Information Collected**  
When you visit Linkstoxx you provide us with two types of information: one of personal information that you voluntarily choose to disclose and that we collect and, secondly, data on the use of the website we collect when you interact with our Website. 

When you register Linkstoxx, you provide certain personal information such as your name, email address, your gender, schools you attended and other personal information you wish to disclose. 

When you use Linkstoxx, you can update your personal profile, your relationships, send messages, perform searches and send invitations, create groups and communicate information in various ways. We retain this information to offer you a service and custom duties. In most cases, we keep it so that, for example, you can find the messages you have sent or consult your list of friends. 

Please note that you publish on the site Linkstoxx.com information (as defined in the Terms of Linkstoxx) at your own risk. While we can not afford to set privacy options to limit access to your data, there is no foolproof security system. We are not able to control the actions of other users with whom you've decided to share your pages and information. We therefore can not guarantee that the content you post on this site will not be seen by unauthorized persons. We are in no way responsible for non-compliance with privacy settings or security measures in force on this site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain visible in the archive pages and cached pages or if other users have copied or stored your content. 

Any misuse or inappropriate use of information provided on Linkstoxx is a violation of the Terms of use Linkstoxx and must be reported by e-mail by writing to [abuse@linkstoxx.com](mailto:abuse@linkstoxx.com).

**Under the Data Protection Act, you have a right to access, modify and delete data concerning you. To exercise this right, you can contact us by e-mail:[privacy@linkstoxx.com](mailto:privacy@linkstoxx.com).**  

**Minors under 13 years**  
Linkstoxx not collect or solicit any information from children under 13 years and does not permit their inclusion. Children under 13 should not register or Linkstoxx us personal information such as name, address, telephone number or email address. No personal information should be provided to Linkstoxx or on the website by minors under 13 years. If we learn to have collected such information from a child under 13 without verification or parental consent, we will delete that information as soon as possible. We recommend that minors aged under 13 ask permission from their parents before sending this information to anyone via the Internet.  
   
**Using information obtained by Linkstoxx**  

When you register Linkstoxx, you create your own profile and your own privacy settings. The profile information - such as your name, email address and your photos - are seen by people of networks you have selected, so you can get in touch with them. We may use your name and email address to send you notifications about new services offered by Linkstoxx might interest you. 

The information in your profile is used mainly by Linkstoxx so you can access and modify, as well as the authorized persons have access in accordance with your privacy settings. If your privacy settings permit, other users can Linkstoxx complete your profile (for example, posting messages on your wall). 

Profile information you submit to Linkstoxx available Linkstoxx users who are members of at least one of the networks you have granted access to your information through your privacy settings (eg school, location, friends your friends, etc..). Your name, the names of your network and your profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results on the network Linkstoxx. This limited information will also be accessible to search engines and others. So your friends can find you and send you an invitation. People who see your name in a search will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship with you (friend, friend of a friend, a member of your networks, etc..) Which gives them access your information (according to your privacy settings). 

By creating a user account Linkstoxx, you authorize Linkstoxx to send you service notifications under the general operation of the site. These messages weekly or monthly informing you of updates to the site, statistics of your account and your network, payments or ongoing. 

Linkstoxx can use the data in your profile without identifying you as an individual screws to third parties. These data allow us in particular to estimate the number of people in your network who like such as music or film, or to customize the advertising and promotions that we offer on Linkstoxx.  

**Links**  
Linkstoxx may contain links to external sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. This privacy policy applies only to features published on Linkstoxx.com and information collected by Linkstoxx.  
   
**Changing or deleting information**  

The control and access to most personal information on Linkstoxx are available from the profile editing tools. Linkstoxx users can always change or delete any information concerning their profile by logging into their account Linkstoxx. Any changes will take effect immediately. Persons wishing to terminate their account Linkstoxx can do so by sending an e-mail to [account@linkstoxx.com ](mailto:account@linkstoxx.com). The traces of the deleted information will be kept for a reasonable period, but will be searchable by any member of Linkstoxx. 

However, when you use the communications functions of the website to share information with other individuals on Linkstoxx (for example, send a personal message to another user Linkstoxx), you generally can not remove such communications.  

**Terms of Use, Notices and Updates**  
Your use of Linkstoxx, and any disputes arising from such use, are subject to this privacy policy and our terms of use and all its provisions conflict resolution, including arbitration, limitation of damages and choice of jurisdiction. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy and our terms of use at any time. The non-substantive changes and clarifications will take effect immediately. As for important updates, they will take effect within thirty days of their posting on the site. If we make changes, we will publish them and we will show the top of this page the new effective date of this policy. If we make any substantial changes to this policy, we will inform you on this page. We invite you to check this Privacy Policy regularly. Unless otherwise indicated, our privacy policy applies to all information we have about you and your account.
